arirang.co.kr 2017-06-21

# Privacy Policy | The World On Arirang

Go to the Contents Go to the menu

## arirang help

### PRIVACY POLICY

## Privacy Policy for Members of Arirang’s Web Site

The Korea International Broadcasting Foundation (hereinafter referred to as “Foundation”) protects users’ personal information according to Article 30 of the Act on the Protection of Personal Information, and has set the following guidelines to ensure that any problems related to personal information are processed swiftly. 

  * #### Article 1 (Purpose of collecting personal information)

① The Foundation collects personal information for the following purposes. The collected personal information is not used for purposes that are not specified below. Should the purposes of using personal information be changed, the Foundation will obtain consent from users according to Article 18 of the Act on the Protection of Personal Information.   
※ For more information on personal information files registered at the Foundation, visit the Ministry of the Interior’s personal information protection portal (privacy.go.kr) → Personal Information Services → View Personal Information → List of Personal Information Files. 
  * #### Article 2 (Duration of Collection and Retention of Personal Information)

① The Foundation collects and retains personal information in line with the relevant laws as well as according to the period that users have agreed upon when submitting their personal information. 
  * #### Article 3 (Provision of personal information to a third party)

The Foundation collects and uses personal information provided by members only according to Article 1 (Purposes of Collecting Personal Information) and only provides personal information to a third party at users’ consent and in line with the relevant laws according to Article 17 of the Act on the Protection of Personal Information. 
  * #### Article 4 (Users’ Rights, Responsibilities and Methods of Exercising Those Rights)

① Users have the following privacy protection rights that they can exercise at any time.   
1\. View personal information  
2\. Correct errors and modify information  
3\. Delete information   
4\. Demand suspension of information processing   
5\. Notify of personal information that has been received from another person   
② The rights specified in Paragraph 1 can be exercised by contacting the Foundation through a written letter, phone call, email or fax. The Foundation shall respond without delay.   
③ In case the user demands a correction of errors in his or her personal information or deletion of certain information, the Foundation shall not use or provide the information in question until the errors are corrected or certain information is deleted.   
④ Users can exercise their rights specified in Paragraph 1 via their legal representatives. However, they must submit a letter of attorney according to Article 11 of the Addendum of the Act on the Protection of Personal Information.   
⑤ Users must not infringe on their own privacy or the privacy of other people collected by the Foundation by violating the Act on the Protection of Personal Information.   

  * #### Article 5 (Destruction of Personal Information) 

① The Foundation immediately destroys users’ personal information as soon as the retention period is over and after achieving the purpose of its collection.   
② If the Foundation needs to retain the provided information in line with the relevant laws even when the agreed retention period is over or after achieving the purpose of its collection, it shall move the personal information in question (or personal information file) to a separate database or another storage space.   
③ Users’ personal information is destroyed as follows.   
1\. Destruction process   
The Foundation destroys personal information (or personal information files) according to a special procedure. The Foundation selects personal information (or personal information file) subject to destruction, obtains approval from the person in charge of personal information protection, and destroys it.   
2\. Destruction method  
The Foundation destroys personal information stored in the form of electronic files using the low level format, which cannot be revived. Personal information stored in the form of paper documents is destroyed by shredding or incineration  

  * #### Article 6 (Ensuring the Safety of Personal Information) 

① The Foundation takes the following measures to ensure the safety of personal information.   
1\. Handling measures: Devising and executing management plans, and regular employee training  
2\. Technical measures: Control of access to the personal information processing system, installation of access control systems, encryption of passwords, and installation of security programs  
3\. Physical measures: Access control in computer and materials storage rooms 
  * #### Article 7 (Staff in Charge of Personal Information Protection) 

① The Foundation designates special personnel to oversee users’ personal information and process complaints and disputes regarding the collection of personal information.   
▶ Staff in charge of personal information protection  Category | Field/position | Name  | Contact Numbers  
---|---|---|---  
Personal information protection superintendent | Management HQ | Kim, Ki-Choon | Phone: 02-3475-5000  
Personal information manager | Management Support Team, Deputy Chief | Bang Seok-chul | Phone: 02-3475-5262  
Email: privacy@arirang.com  
Fax: 02-3475-5059  
  
② Users can inquire the staff in charge of personal information protection about any matters, complaints and disputes related to personal information that they have submitted to use the Foundation’s services. The Foundation shall respond to users’ inquiries without delay. 
  * #### Article 8 (Demand to View Users’ Personal Information)

① Users can demand from the following staff to view their personal information according to Article 35 of the Act on the Protection of Personal Information. The Foundation shall try to process the request as soon as possible.   
▶ Department in charge of personal information viewing   
Department: Viewers Satisfaction Team   
Person in charge: Lee Taek-soo   
Phone: 02-3475-5260, email: tslee@arirang.com, fax: 02-3475-5115 

② Users can also view their personal information by visiting the Ministry of Interior’s personal information protection portal (privacy.go.kr).   
▶ Ministry of Interior personal information protection portal (privacy.go.kr) → Personal Information Services → View Personal Information (authorization required) 

  * #### Article 9 (Remedies for Infringement of Rights and Interests)

① Users can file complaints when their privacy has been infringed.   
▶ Complaints regarding privacy violations   
\- Department: Management Support Team  
\- Person in charge: Bang Seok-chul  
\- Phone: 02-3475-5262, privacy@arirang.com, fax: 02-3475-5059  
② Users can request help from the following organizations in case they are not satisfied with the way the Foundation addressed their complaints.   
▶ Higher organization (Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism)  
\- Responsibilities: Reports of privacy violations, consultations   
\- Website: mcst.go.kr  
\- Phone: 044-203-2269  
\- Address: Bldg. 15, Sejong Government Complex, 388 Galmae-ro, Sejong 30119   
Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, Sejong Government Complex 

▶ Privacy Violation Report Center (operated by Korea Internet & Security Agency)   
\- Responsibilities: Reports of privacy violations, consultations  
\- Website: privacy.kisa.or.kr   
\- Phone: 118   
\- Address: Privacy Violation Report Center, Korea Internet & Security Agency, 135 Jungdae-ro, Songpa-gu, Seoul 138-950

▶ Personal Information Dispute Mediation Committee (operated by Korea Internet & Security Agency)   
\- Responsibilities: Personal information disputes arbitration, collective dispute arbitration (civil arbitration)   
\- Website: privacy.kisa.or.kr   
\- Phone: 118   
\- Address: Privacy Violation Report Center, Korea Internet & Security Agency, 135 Jungdae-ro, Songpa-gu, Seoul 138-950

▶ Cybercrime Investigation Department, Supreme Prosecutors’ Office: 02-3480-3573 (www.spo.go.kr)

▶ Cyber Terror Response Center, National Police Agency: 1566-0112 (www.netan.go.kr)

③ Users whose rights or interests were violated by the chiefs of public agencies processing users’ complaints can request an administrative trial according to the Administrative Appeals Act.   
※ For more information on administrative trials, visit the Website of the Administrative Appeals Commission (simpan.go.kr). 

  * #### Article 10 (Modified Personal Information Collection Agreement)

The modified personal information collection agreement takes effect on July 26, 2016. 

Click [here](http://www.arirang.com/Help/Privacy_Policy_2015.asp?sys_lang=Eng) to see the previous version of Personal Information Collection Agreement.
